netbanx.com 2018-03-25

# Paysafe - Privacy Policy

Paysafe Group Limited and any of its group companies (together “ **Paysafe** ” or " **we** " or “ **our** ”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This notice (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to in it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. It applies to:

  * the website/portal features and services provided to you when you visit our websites, portals or our payment panels our clients may use on their websites;
  * when you apply to use and/or use Paysafe’s products and services (including any loyalty or reward schemes, whether points-based or otherwise (‘ **Loyalty** ’ or ‘ **Promotion** ’)); 
  * your use of software including terminals, mobile and desktop applications provided by Paysafe; and
  * email, other electronic messages including SMS, telephone, web chat, website/portal and other communications between you and Paysafe.

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting Paysafe websites, including www.paysafe.com, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this notice.

Paysafe takes a ‘layered approach’ to explaining its privacy practices, as recommended by regulators. This means that we endeavour to provide you with only the relevant privacy information for the Paysafe service being utilised and we will often use ‘short form’ privacy notices, such as this website privacy notice, to do so. Should you wish to view the comprehensive privacy notice, please use the contact us section or click here. Contact us details are provided at the end of the notice, for feedback or any privacy enquiries you may have.

## INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU

We may collect and process data about you to operate effectively and provide you with the best experiences with our products. You may provide some of this information to us, for example by filling in forms on one of our websites, participating in one of our events or by corresponding with by us phone, e-mail, web chat or otherwise. We may collect some of it through automatic means, for example by using cookies when you visit our websites. We may also obtain data about you from third parties.

## USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION

We use information we collect about you to provide you with the products we offer, to notify you about changes to our products and to improve our products. We also use this information to provide you with information about other products we or selected third parties offer which are similar to the ones you have used or enquired about or we think may be of interest to you.

## DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We will not disclose your personal data to anyone except as described in this notice.

We may share your personal information with any company in the Paysafe Group Limited group of companies.

We may share your personal information with third parties to provide you with the products we offer, with suppliers working on our behalf, where we have your permission, or where we are required or permitted to do so by law. We may also share your personal information with third parties to prevent crime and reduce risk, if required to do so by law, where we deem it appropriate to do so, to respond to legal process or to protect the rights or property of Paysafe, our customers or others.

## WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA AND DATA SECURITY

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, stored at and processed in a destination outside the European Economic Area (" **EEA** "). By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy notice.

If we have given you (or if you have chosen) a password, access code or any other secure means or access or authentication which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential and complying with our instructions. You must not share credentials with anyone else, and you authorise Paysafe to act upon instructions and information from any person that enters your credentials.

The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## YOUR RIGHTS

Where applicable, you may have certain rights under data protection legislation, including the right to object to direct marketing and the right to see the personal information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure it is accurate and up to date. If, where applicable, you would like a copy of the personal information we hold about you, please see the Contact Us section. There is a £10 fee within the UK and, where applicable, fees for other jurisdictions are available on request. For a summary of the other rights available, please refer to the comprehensive privacy notice.

## COOKIES

Our website uses “cookies” and other technologies, which store small amounts of information on your computer or device, to allow certain information from your web browser to be collected. Cookies are widely used on the internet and allow a website/portal to recognise a user’s device, without uniquely identifying the individual person using the computer. These technologies help to make it easier for you to log on and use the site, provide feedback to us as to which parts of the website you visit, so we can assess the effectiveness of the site and provide a better user experience or to serve Paysafe adverts to you whilst browsing other sites.

For more information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage, block and delete them, see [www.allaboutcookies.org ](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)and our Cookies Policy, which is available on all of our websites. You may also be able to configure your browser not to accept cookies, although please bear in mind that this may affect your ability to use the services we provide.

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY NOTICE

Any changes we may make to our privacy notice in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy notice.

## CONTACT US

All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed, or if you wish to exercise any of your rights, you should write to the address below, marked FAO Legal Department or [contact us](mailto:Data.Privacy@Paysafe.com).
